You can win $1,000,000 and all you have
to do to enter is buy our brand new book
that drops September [music] 1st.
Growing up, I thought reading was
boring, so I partnered with James
Patterson here. Oh, don't press that
yet. Uh to write a book.
>> You told me we were going to blow up
something.
>> Yes, we will after you tell them about
the book.
>> The most dangerous games, and that's
exactly what it is. It's the best book
I've ever written.
>> Yeah, and it's very innovative. It's
captivating. You're going to be hooked
until the very end while reading this
book. It's something you're not going to
be Oh, did he press the button? He
pressed the button.
>> Totally worth it.
>> Go buy the book. That was crazy.
>> That's as exciting as a book.